<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Kingdoms>

	<Kingdom
		id="galactic_republic"
		owner="Hero.palpatine"
		banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.764.764.1.0.0"
		primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
		secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
		label_color="FF850C6D"
		color="FF39223F"
		color2="FFDE9953"
		alternative_color="FFffffff"
		alternative_color2="FF660653"
		culture="Culture.galactic_republic"
		settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
		name="Galactic Republic"
		short_name="Republic"
		title="Galactic Republic"
		ruler_title="Supreme Chancellor"
		text="For the past 25,000 years, the Galactic Republic has stood unequivocally as the supreme authority in galactic affairs. Comprised of tens of thousands of member worlds spanning the entire breadth of the known galaxy, the sheer magnitude of resources the Republic has available is nigh unfathomable. However, nothing lasts forever, and many believe the twilight of the Republic is upon us. Rampant corruption and bloated bureaucracy have engulfed every facet of the Republic, catalyzing the Separatist Crisis, an event in which the newly formed Confederacy of Independent Systems was born. Today, millions of Clone Troopers back the Republic as they battle the Confederacy to bring them back into the fold.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship
				kingdom="Kingdom.separatist"
				value="-1"
				isAtWar="true" />
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy
				id="policy_feudal_inheritance" />
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>

	<Kingdom
		id="separatist"
		owner="Hero.dooku"
		banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.764.764.1.0.0"
		primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
		secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
		label_color="FF850C6D"
		color="FF39223F"
		color2="FFDE9953"
		alternative_color="FFffffff"
		alternative_color2="FF660653"
		culture="Culture.separatist"
		settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
		name="Confederacy of Independent Systems"
		short_name="CIS"
		title="Confederacy of Independent Systems"
		ruler_title="Head of State"
		text="Wracked with political corruption and decaying influence, the total collapse of the Republic seemed inevitable. Thousands of discontented Republic worlds needed a savior, and one would emerge to save them. Count Dooku of Serreno gave the Raxus Address, admonishing the Republic and the Jedi Order for allowing corruption to spread with impunity. Shortly following this address, Dooku founded the Confederacy of Independent Systems, promising free trade, drastically reduced taxation, and freedom from corruption. Tens of thousands of worlds answered his call, forming a government capable of contesting the might of the Republic. With a newly created army of millions of Battle Droids, they seek to defend their sovereignty against the Galactic Republic.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship
				kingdom="Kingdom.galactic_republic"
				value="-1"
				isAtWar="true" />
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy
				id="policy_feudal_inheritance" />
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>

	<Kingdom
		id="neutral_systems"
		owner="Hero.satine"
		banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.764.764.1.0.0"
		primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
		secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
		label_color="FF850C6D"
		color="FF39223F"
		color2="FFDE9953"
		alternative_color="FFffffff"
		alternative_color2="FF660653"
		culture="Culture.neutral_systems"
		settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
		name="Council of Neutral Systems"
		short_name="Neutral Systems"
		title="Council of Neutral Systems"
		ruler_title="Chancellor"
		text="In a galaxy embroiled in a full-scale conflict, many worlds did not wish to align themselves with either side of the Clone Wars. Instead, they chose peace, seeking diplomacy and free trade with both sides of the war. These systems formed the Council of Neutral Systems, a coalition of worlds guided by Duchess Satine Kryze of Mandalore. Together, they use their voice to bring about an end to the Clone Wars and restore lasting peace to the galaxy. But, no one can remain neutral for long. The Death Watch and other factions threaten the tranquility of the Neutral Systems, and may soon lead to Republic or Separatist intervention if they cannot quell these outside threats.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy
				id="policy_feudal_inheritance" />
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>

	<Kingdom
		id="death_watch"
		owner="Hero.vizsla"
		banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.764.764.1.0.0"
		primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
		secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
		label_color="FF850C6D"
		color="FF39223F"
		color2="FFDE9953"
		alternative_color="FFffffff"
		alternative_color2="FF660653"
		culture="Culture.death_watch"
		settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
		name="Death Watch"
		short_name="Death Watch"
		title="Death Watch"
		ruler_title="Mand'alor"
		text="The Kyr'tsad, known in Basic as Death Watch, unequivocally rejects the pacifist teachings of the Anti-Mandalore Satine Kryze and her New Mandalorians. Instead they follow the ways of their ancestors, adhering to the Resol'nare, or the Six Actions, and worshipping the Mandalorian dieties of old. Through their religious zealotry and idealism, the Death Watch view themselves as the true Mando'ade, or Children of Mand'alor, and as such will do everyhing in their power to take back Mand'alor and revive the ancient ways.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy
				id="policy_feudal_inheritance" />
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>

	<Kingdom
		id="crime_syndicates"
		owner="Hero.jabba"
		banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.764.764.1.0.0"
		primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
		secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
		label_color="FF850C6D"
		color="FF39223F"
		color2="FFDE9953"
		alternative_color="FFffffff"
		alternative_color2="FF660653"
		culture="Culture.crime_syndicates"
		settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
		name="Crime Syndicates"
		short_name="Crime Syndicates"
		title="Crime Syndicates"
		ruler_title="Excellency"
		text="Comprised of the Hutt Cartel, Black Sun, and the Pyke Syndicate, the Crime Syndicates have a hand in almost everything illicit throughout the galaxy. From spice to slaves, the syndicates involve themselves in any venture that generates credits, regardless of the morality. They control a large swathe of territory in the Outer Rim, mostly keeping out of galactic affairs. Instead, they use the calamity surrounding the Clone Wars to spread their tendrils and increase their vast wealth.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy
				id="policy_feudal_inheritance" />
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>

<Kingdoms/>

